A Guide to the William J. “Bill” Elvin Collection, 1914-2004, bulk 1963-2003
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 1: McLean Providence Journal Subject Files, 1914-2004
  - McLean Citizens Association - Old Dominion Citizens Association 1913-1914 Minutes, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - McLean Citizens Association - Transportation Committee, 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - McLean Citizens Association - Tysons Corner, 1984-1993 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - McLean Citizens Foundation, 1980-1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - McLean Community Center, 1963-2003 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - McLean Community Center - Memorandum of Understanding, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - McLean Community Center - Youth Center, 1984-1993 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - McLean Community Center - Youth Center - Clippings, 1984-1992 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - McLean Day - Copies of Programs, 1922-1923 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - McLean Development Plans, 1971-2001 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - McLean Government Center, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - McLean Grove, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - McLean High School, 1966-1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - McLean Historical Society, 1991-2003 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - McLean Historical Society - Research for Historical Marker, 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - McLean History, 1961-1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - McLean History - Directories, 1964-1972 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - McLean History - Martha Catlin Manuscript, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - McLean History - Newspaper Clippings, 1961-2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - McLean House, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - McLean Little League Baseball, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - McLean Orchestra, 1986-2003 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - McLean Orchestra - Programs, 1985-2002 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - McLean Planning - The Reserve, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - McLean Planning 1965 - Proposal for a Master Plan for the Pimmit Run Area, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - McLean Planning 1966 - McLean Master Plan, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - McLean Planning 1967-1968, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - McLean Planning 1969, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - McLean Planning 1970, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - McLean Planning 1972 - McLean Central Business District - Design Standards, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - McLean Planning 1983 - Sharon Lodge, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - McLean Planning 1985, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - McLean Planning 1985 - Salona Mobil, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - McLean Planning 1988 - McLean Central Business District Task Force Report, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - McLean Planning 1989 - McLean Planning District Area II Background Paper, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - McLean Planning 1990 - McLean Planning District Special Development Areas, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - McLean Planning 1991, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - McLean Planning 1994 - Pozez Rezoning Application, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - McLean Planning 1995 - Comprehensive Plan for Fairfax County Area II, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - McLean Planning 1996 - McLean Central Business District Urban Design Manual Draft, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - McLean Planning 1997, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - McLean Planning 1998, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - McLean Planning 1999, 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - McLean Planning Committee, 1963-1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - McLean Planning Committee, 1990-1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - McLean Planning Committee, 2000-2002 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - McLean Planning Committee - Central Business District, 1967-1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - McLean Post Office, 1966-1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - McLean Presbyterian Church, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - McLean Project for the Arts, 2001-2004 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - McLean Providence Journal - Advertising and Subscription, 1968-1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - McLean Providence Journal - Correspondence, 1966-1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - McLean Providence Journal - History, 1982-1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - McLean Providence Journal - Letterhead, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - McLean Providence Journal - Miscellaneous News Clippings, 1969-1983 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - McLean Providence Journal - News Clippings on Local Newspapers, 1966-1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - McLean Providence Journal - Printing Materials, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - McLean Providence Journal - Statement of Ownership, Management and Circulation, 1952-1999 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - McLean Providence Journal - The Journal Building and Office Leasing with Francis Koenig, 1966-1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - McLean Revitalization Corporation, 1999-2003 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - McLean Rezoning, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - McLean Savings & Loan, 1977-1988 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - McLean Settlers Clan, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - McLean Square Access Road, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - McLean Trees Committee, 1984-2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - McLean White House, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - McLean Youth Inc., 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Meadow Run Homeowners Association, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Meals on Wheels, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Meals Tax, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Mehr, Stanley, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Merit Pay - Career Level II Schools, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Merrywood, 1962-1995 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Merrywood, Salona, Burling - History, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Metro, 1963-1983 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Metro, 1961-1986 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Metro - 1973 Impact Study, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Metro - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission, 1965-1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Metro - Stations & Bus Connections, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Metro - WV&M Coach Company, 1966-1971 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Metzger, Evelyn, 1984-2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Mitre Corporation, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Monopole Zoning, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Moon, Sun Myung, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Moore, Audrey, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Moran, James P., 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Morgan-Foretich Custody Case, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - National Capitol Planning Commission, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - National Science Foundation Move, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - National Wildlife Federation - Recycling Drop-Off Center Zoning Application, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Nordstrom Slave Labor Case, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Northern Virginia Baptist Ministers Conference - Discrimination, 1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Northern Virginia Center - University of Virginia, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Northern Virginia Community Appearance Alliance, Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 1964-1988 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Northern Virginia News Association - Membership List, Undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Northern Virginia Regional Park Authority, 1966-1991 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Nutri/System Lawsuits, Undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - NVR Bank - Embezzlement Case, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - O'Brien, James S., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - O'Brien, Marian, Undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Odom, Bill, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Old Dominion Square, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Othman, Fred - Property, 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Pahlavi, Reza (Shah), 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Paisley, Melvyn R., 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Parkouts - Garbage Disposal, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Parks - Fairfax County Park Authority, 1965-1976 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Patowmack Canal, 1987-1990 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Patowmack Power Partners Proposed Power Plant, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - "Peace Divided" in NOVA, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Pension Tax Plan, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Perot, H. Ross, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Persian Gulf War - Kasim Mashat, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Phillips, Rufus, 1974-1978 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Pierce, Merrily, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Pimmit Run, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Plan Review - Fairfax County Comprehensive Plan Review Process, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Planning - 1972 American Institute of Architects, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Planning - Miscellaneous, 1966-1995 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Pleasant Grove Methodist Church, 1963-2000 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Police - Neighborhood Watch, 1977-1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Post Office Story - Local Management Issues, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Postal Service, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Potomac College, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Potomac River Basin [contains photographs], 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Potomac School, 1989-1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Preston's McLean Drugs, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Primark Corporation, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Project WORD (Working and Organizing Resources for People with Disabilities), 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Property Owners Association Act, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Providence Baptist Church, 1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Prudential Health Care, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Questech Inc., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Rabies, 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Radon, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Real Estate, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Recycling - Fairfax County Waste Reduction and Recycling Program, 1978-1997 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Redistricting, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Report of the Citizens Advisory Committee on the Reapportionment of Districts, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Residential Permit Parking District, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Restaurants, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Richards, Lilla and Stan, 1972-1990 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - River Towers Zoning Reports, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Robb, Charles and Lynda, 1978-2001 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Rokeby estate, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Rollison, Jack, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Rotunda Condominium, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Route 7 - Interstates 66 and 495 Study, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - RPC District Proposed Revision to Minimum Lot Sizes, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Rust, Thomas D., Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Safety Helmet Bill, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Saint John’s Episcopal Church, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Sanders, David G., 1991 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Sanders-Scott / Recount Controversy, 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Schar Colvill Green/ Lewinsville Road Rezoning, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Schar, Dwight C. - NVR Inc., 1987-1991 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - School and Civic League of McLean, Virginia, 1914-1954 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Schultz, Leslie P., 1984 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Scott's Run Nature Preserve, 1980-2002 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Security Alarms - Regulations, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Semales, Bob - Leukemia, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Service League of Northern Virginia, 1978-1983 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Services for Seniors in Fairfax County, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Sex Education, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Shacochis, John P. and Bob, 1975-1987 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - SHARE Inc., 1987-1992 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Signs - Illegal Postings, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Smoking - Fairfax County Policy, 1977-1988 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Solid Waste - Tax Increase, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Spring Hill Elementary School, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Spring Hill Recreation Center, 1983-1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Springfield Bypass, 1981-1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - St. Dunstan's Episcopal Church, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - St. John’s Catholic School, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Stalcup’s Fruit Stand, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Starr, Kenneth and Alice, 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Stitt, David T., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Storm Drainage, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Strauss, Jane K. "Janie", 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Swinks Mill - Virginia Power Planned Substation, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Swinson, James D., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Synagogue - Rodef Shalom, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Taxpayers - Citizens for Sensible Taxation, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - T-Cas Building (1749 Old Meadow Road), Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Team Network Corporation, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - TEDI - Telecommunications Devices for the Deaf, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Terry, Mary Sue, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Thoburn, Robert L., 1988-2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Thrasher Road and VDOT Sidewalk Maintenance, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Tibet, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Tollgate of Falls Church [includes photograph], Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Tower Club, 1988-1992 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Trails - Georgetown Pike extension, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Transportation, 1966-1990 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Transportation - National Capital Beltway, 1991-1999 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Trayhern, Robert J., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Trees, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Tribble, Edwin, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Trinity United Methodist Church - Organ, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Trustee Sales, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Turner-Fairbanks Highway Research Center, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Tysons, 1988-1997 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Tysons - The Galleria at Tysons II News Releases, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Tysons Cloverleaf Partnership - Rezoning Controversy, 1986-1991 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Tysons Corner - Article Drafts by Elvin, 1990-1997 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Tysons Corner - Ash Grove - Sherman Family, 1986-1998 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Tysons Corner - Gannett Company, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Tysons Corner - History, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Tysons Corner - Mayo Stuntz, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Tysons Corner - Nordstrom, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Tysons Corner - Planning, 1990-1997 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Tysons Corner - Planning Commission Verbatim Excerpts, 1977-1988 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Tysons Corner - Storm Farm, Randolph Seeley, John Ulfelder, 1988-1997 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Tysons Corner - West Group, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Tysons Corner (a), 1980-2002 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Tysons Corner (b), 1968-1997 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Tysons Corner 1999, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Tysons Corner Center, 1977-1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Tysons Corner Center Suit, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Tysons Corner Marriott, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Tysons Corner Play and Learn Children's Center, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Tysons Galleria, 1980-1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Tysons II, 1981-1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Tysons II - McLean Rezoning, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Tysons Towers Crescent - Tycon Center, 1991-1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Tysons Transportation Association, 1981-1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Tysons-Pimmit Park, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Tytran - Tree Planting Project, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Udall, Morris, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Underground Utilities, 1984-1991 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - United Way, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Utilities - Electricity, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Utilities - Sewers, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Utilities - Telephone, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Washington Trade Exchange, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - West Group - Rezoning Proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - West Group 1999, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Women, 1972-1997 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Writings - 1998 Article Drafts by Elvin, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Writings - 1999 Article Drafts by Elvin, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Writings - 2000 Article Drafts by Elvin, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Writings - 2001 Article Drafts by Elvin, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Writings - 2001 Article Drafts by Elvin, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Writings - 2001 Obituary Drafts by Elvin, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Writings - 2002 Article Drafts by Elvin, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Writings - 2002 Article Drafts by Elvin, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Writings - 2002 Research for Article Drafts by Elvin, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Writings - Published Articles by Elvin, 1999-2003 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Writings - Published Obituaries by Elvin, 2001-2003 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Zoning - 1971 New Applications for Land, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Zoning - Rezoning Applications, 1964-1971 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Series 2: McLean Providence Journal Subject Files, 1925-2004
  - ABC Stores, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Ablard, James E., 1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural and Forestal District Zoning, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - AIDS, 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Air and Space Museum - Dulles, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Air Raid Siren, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Airplane Accident 1977 - McLean, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Akre, Jack, 1996-2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Alcohol & Drugs, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Alden Theatre, 1992-2001 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Alden, Robert A., 1967-2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Alger, Camp - Centennial Celebration, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Allen, George, 1968-1997 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Allen, Paul R., 19,711,996 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Alternative House, Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - American Association of University Women, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - American Legion, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Ames, Aldrich, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Amphora Restaurant, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Anderson, Gus and Harriet, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Andrews, Byron, Coleman, Peter, Harriette, Minerva, Robert T., 1991-2001 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Animal Shelter, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Apartments, 1963-1997 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Appling, Arneida, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Arleigh Burke Pavilion, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Arlington - Development of Wester Estate, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Arlington Cemetery, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Arlington Hospital Joint Venture News, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Arundel, Peter and Arthur, 1978-2001 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Ash Grove, 1988-2000 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Assessments, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Audubon Society, 1984-1990 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Auerbach, Jan, 1994-1999 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Ayers, Mrs. Henry, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Babson, Fred, 1967-1999 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Bacon’s Castle, Undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Ball, Mottrom, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Ballantrae, 1964-1999 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Ballantrae Ski Club, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Balmacara - Housing Development, Undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Bandar, Bin Sultan, 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Banks, 1994-1999 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Baseball Stadium MLB, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Bat-House - Kirby Road Demolition, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Bayes, Guy M., 1994 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - BDM International Inc., 1983-1997 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Beall, Mrs, 1995-2000 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - L.L. Bean Store, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Beavers, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Becker, Herb, 1991-1997 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Bengston, Elise, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Berger, Ernest J., 1987-1995 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Berkowitz, Rabbi Laszlo, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Bersie, William A., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Bersoff, Edward, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Beyer, Donald S., 1993-1997 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Bicksler, Edna, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Bienvenue, 1967-2001 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Bilidas, George, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Billman, Tom, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Bissell, Suzanne, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Black Community, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Blackford, Jan, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Blazek, Mark, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Bles, Marcus, Undated (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Blight, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Bliss, Richard W., 1993 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Blueberry Hill - Cohousing, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Bobzien, David, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Bombing - Kenya, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Bond, Dewey, Undated (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Bonds, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Boston, Bernie, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Boswell, Charles, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Boyle, Fay, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Bradley, Harriet F, 1963-1975 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Brady, James S., 1993 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Brand, Michael, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Bridges, Undated (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Brighton Gardens - Marriott Development, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Brink, Robert, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Britten, Burdick, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Brock, Geraldine, Undated (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Brookins, H. Hartford, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Brooks, Cornell, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Bross, John, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Brown, Betty, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Brown, Brickman, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Broyhill, Joel T., 1956-1999 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Brundage, Dean E., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Bryant, Wilbert, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Bryn Mawr Park, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1979-1993 (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Buchanan, Patrick and Bay, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - Buildings - Dana Gumb, Jr editorial on Frances Koenig's Ingleside Building, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Burk, Carl, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - Burke Lake, Undated (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - Burke, Kaye Sloan, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - Burks, Craighill, Undated (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - Burns, Don, Undated (Box 15, Folder 100)
  - Burton, Joe Allen, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - Bush, George W., 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Businesses - McLean [contains photographs], 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - Butler, Henry, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - Byrd, Harry F., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Byrd, Robert, 1998-2002 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Byrne, Leslie, 1992-1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Byrnes, Bill, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Cable TV, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Cain, Leighton, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Caldwell, Dr. Teressa, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Callahan, Vincent and Dot, 1967-2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Capital Beltway, 1995-2003 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Capital One Bank, 2000-2002 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Carderock, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Carmichael, Warren, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Carper, O.V., Wallace, Bright, John, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Carrico, Harry L., Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Cartier Jewelers, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Casolaro, J. Daniel, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Catholic Diocese of Arlington, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Center for Innovative Technology, 1984-2003 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Central Business District - McLean, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Century National Bank, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Chain Bridge, 1969-1978 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Chain Bridge Road - Improvements, 1966-1984 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Chamber of Commerce - Installation Luncheon, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Chambers, Glen, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Chaney, Renee, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Charley’s Place Restaurant, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Chase, Stanhope, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Chelsea Road - Improvements, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Chesapeake Bay, 1992-2003 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Chesterbrook Presbyterian Church - Senior Housing, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Chesterbrook Road - Improvements, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Chesterbrook School, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Chesterbrook Shopping Center, 1991-1997 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Chevy Chase Bank, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Christopher, Beverly, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Churches, 1988-2000 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Churchill Road, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Citizens for Sensible Taxation, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Civic Place, 2000-2002 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Civil Defense, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Civil War, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Civitan Club, Undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Clark, Clyde, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Clarke, Charles, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Claude Moore Farm at Turkey Run, 1971-1996 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Clay, Edwin S. III, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 46)